Guide to the Bound for Glory records, 1969-2015.
Bound for Glory records, 1969-2015.
- Encore Tapes
  - Bound For Glory - Return of Encore Tape (#428 06-Dec-1981 thru #483 07-Aug-1983), Digital only
    Bound for Glory Show #: 428 - 483
- Miscellaneous Tapes
  - Performer unknown, December 25, 1983; tr-17859 (Box 2)
    Bound for Glory Show #: unknown
  - Performer unknown, December 25, 1983; tr-17860 (Box 2)
  - Bill Staines, May 19, 1985; tr-17862 (Box 2)
  - Pete Seger, August 26, 1990; tr-17869 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, August 26, 1990; tr-17870 (Box 2)
    On label: Queen
  - Performer unknown, December 16, 1990; tr-17877 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, January 6, 1991; tr-17878 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, January 6, 1991; tr-17879 (Box 2)
    Also labeled with date March 4, 2001 and performer Mark Rust
  - Performer unknown, January 13, 1991; tr-17880 (Box 2)
    On label: "None Such" and "Wizard of Oz, Billy Wizard, Blackbird Song Side A"
  - Performer unknown, October 13, 1991; tr-17884 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, October 13, 1991; tr-17885 (Box 2)
    Also labeled with dates October 14, 1990 and September 15, 1991
  - Performer unknown, December 15, 1991; tr-17888 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, January 17, 1993; tr-17898 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, August 15, 1993; tr-17899 (Box 2)
    Date on label is August 14, 1993; label also lists "Country Sampler and Town"
  - Performer unknown, August 15, 1993; tr-17918 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, March 13, 1994; tr-17902 (Box 2)
    Date on label is March 12, 1994
  - Performer unknown, March 17, 1996; tr-17882 (Box 2)
  - Performer unknown, Date unknown; tr-17866 (Box 2)
  - Wicky Sears, Date unknown; tr-17867 (Box 2)
  - Dady Brothers, Date unknown; tr-17868 (Box 2)